<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Coppola Winery and Skincare</title>
	<atom:link href="https://jxi74.github.io/coppola/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://jxi74.github.io/coppola</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 04:53:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Uvavita: New Skin Care Line Utilizes Grape Seed Oils and Extracts Founded by Roman Coppola</title>
		<link>https://jxi74.github.io/coppola/uvavita-new-skin-care-line-utilizes-grape-seed-oils-and-extractsfounded-by-roman-coppola/</link>
					<comments>https://jxi74.github.io/coppola/uvavita-new-skin-care-line-utilizes-grape-seed-oils-and-extractsfounded-by-roman-coppola/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[jasonmatthew07]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 04:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://jxi74.github.io/coppola/?p=2656</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Uvavita: New Skin Care Line Utilizes Grape Seed Oils and Extracts Founded by Roman Coppola (Napa, Ca) Uvavita, a line of innovative skin care products, has entered the market with products that make use of grape seed oils and extracts, harvested from the Coppola&#8217;s successful local winery. The name is derived from the Latin words [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="wp-block-uagb-container uagb-block-ae0bc409 alignfull uagb-is-root-container"><div class="uagb-container-inner-blocks-wrap">
<div class="wp-block-uagb-advanced-heading uagb-block-59973544"><h1 class="uagb-heading-text">Uvavita: New Skin Care Line Utilizes Grape Seed Oils and Extracts Founded by Roman Coppola</h1></div>
</div></div>



<p class="has-background" style="background-color:#f3f2ee">(Napa, Ca) Uvavita, a line of innovative skin care products, has entered the market with products that make use of grape seed oils and extracts, <br>harvested from the Coppola&#8217;s successful local winery. The name is derived from the Latin words “Uva” for seed, and “Vita” for life,<br>together meaning “The seed of life.” The grape seeds in Uvavita products tap into the anti-aging potential of grape seeds’ polyphenols.<br>Founded three years ago, Uvavita was developed and nourished by Roman Coppola and his four friends who are dedicated to making a <br>difference in the skin care world.<br><br>Roman grew up in California’s Napa Valley, where his father, Francis Ford Coppola, a famous film maker for films such as “The Godfather” series,<br>owns a vineyard that produces a very successful line of wines. It was here where the idea sparked for Uvavita. “Grape seeds are a by-product of <br>wine production and normally go unused. We are proud to have discovered a valuable benefit in something that is usually considered a waste product.”<br>Coppola describes. He further accentuates the brand’s commitment to purity and sustainability by stating, “We use a wine permeate instead of harsh <br>solvents to extract the phenols – it’s a pure, handmade way of extracting them. We’re coming at this from a wine-making tradition and from the place <br>that is known for the finest grapes in the country.”<br><br>Uvavita’s product lineup consists of five distinct options:<br><br>1. Day Moisturizing Cream<br>2. Night Nourishing Cream<br>3. Exfoliating Dead Sea Mud Mask<br>4. Gentle Foaming Face Cleanser<br>5. Hydrating Body Lotion<br><br>The prices for these products range from between $28 &#8211; $56. Uvavita aims to produce quality <br>products that are accessible to a wide range of consumers.<br><br>Despite the business being under a year old, Uvavita has already broken into the forefront of 25 specialty stores, including Sephora.<br>Business is going so well, Coppola plans to expand the distribution of the product up to 80 stores by the end of this year. In effect, <br>making the reach of their products over three times what it already is.<br><br>Stephen Bock, Sephora’s Director of Merchandising, recently made comments on the popularity of grape seed extract-based products,<br>expressing, “Grape Seed extract-based products are on fire right now in terms of sales.”<br><br>For more information about Uvavita and their new line of products, which are also sold on their website, please visit www.uvavita.com</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://jxi74.github.io/coppola/uvavita-new-skin-care-line-utilizes-grape-seed-oils-and-extractsfounded-by-roman-coppola/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
